Christian Bassey Software Engineer

07083978372 createwithcorenlog@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Methodical Mobile focused developer experienced in software development processes and optimal testing strategies. Helps teams produce exceptional products by offering in-depth quality assurance support. Open and clear communicator with good multitasking skills, organized nature and strong attention to detail.

Passionate about writing value adding algorithms and applications.

I manifest industries from life's lemons.

Work History

September 2022 - Current
Goke-Remi College - Lagos, Lagos State
Web Development Teacher
Passionately working to on-board 13+ kids into software through Web services training.

April 2020 - Current
Independent Work
Freelancer

Fully committed to writing value adding algorithms and applications that scale beautifully and are easy to manage

Working with Dart/Flutter, Golang, Svelte

Education

February 2018 - Current University of Calabar Crossriver State Bachelor Of Applied Science Microbiology And Immunology

November 2022 - Current African Leadership University Kenya (Remote) Certification Software Engineering

Skills

Web application development using Svelte Software Development using Rust (OOP Methodology) Student-centered teaching